Inventory of the Ted Dalton Papers 1933-1978, 1952-1959
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Federal Judgeship, 1958-1960. (Box 12-13)
  - Correspondence, 1958-1960. (Box 12-13)
    - Correspondence, June - Dec. 1964. (Box-folder 13:18)
      Correspondents include Davis Y. Paschall.
  - Speeches, 1958-1960. (Box 12-13)
    - Speeches, 1958. (Box-folder 12:6)
    - Speeches, 1958. (Box-folder 12:8)
    - Speeches, 1959. (Box-folder 12:22)
    - Speeches, 1959. (Box-folder 12:23)
    - Speeches, 1960. (Box-folder 12:25)
  - News Clippings, 1958-1960. (Box 12-13)
    - News Clippings and Letters to Attorney General William P. Rogers, 1958. (Box-folder 12:18)
      Material relate to the Judgeship.
    - News Clippings, 1960. (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Other papers, 1958-1960. (Box 12-13)
    - Virginia Senate Bills, 1958. (Box-folder 12:7)
    - Induction as U. S. Dist. Judge for Western Virginia, 1959. (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Legal Opinions, 1958-1960. (Box 12-13)
    - Legal Opinions, 1960. (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Legal Opinions, 1961. (Box-folder 13:9)
    - Legal Opinions, 1962. (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Legal Opinions, 1962. (Box-folder 13:13)
    - Legal Opinions, 1963. (Box-folder 13:14)
    - Legal Opinions, 1964. (Box-folder 13:19)
    - Legal Opinions and Correspondence, 1964. (Box-folder 13:20)
      Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller.
  Series 10: Papers
- Papers, 1948-1982. (Box 14)
  - Correspondence, 1965-1978. (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1965. (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Correspondence, 1966. (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Correspondence, 1966. (Box-folder 14:4)
      Includes Honorary Litt. D. announcement by Milligan College.
    - Correspondence, 1968. (Box-folder 14:6)
      1 Letter from Albertis S. Harrison.
    - Correspondence, 1966 - 1978. (Box-folder 14:18)
      Correspondents include Mills E. Godwin,Harry F. Byrd, Jr., Mamie Eisenhower, Caspar Weinberger, Mrs. Thomas B. Stanley, William M. Tuck, A. S. Harrison, Jr., J. Edgar Hoover, A. E. Dick Howard, Linwood D. Holton, General R. Ford, John Dalton.
    - Correspondence and Speeches, 1970 - 1971. (Box-folder 14:21)
  - Speeches, 1950-1982. (Box 14)
    - Lewis F. Powell's Speech on Const. Rev., 1969. (Box-folder 14:13)
    - Honorary Litt. D. from College of William and Mary, 1972. (Box-folder 14:16)
      Speech and clipping.
    - Speeches, 1950. (Box-folder 14:19)
    - Speeches, 1951. (Box-folder 14:20)
    - Speeches and Clippings, 1980-1982. (Box-folder 14:24)
  - News Clippings, 1948-1977. (Box 14)
    - News Clippings, 1948, and 1964 - 1967. (Box-folder 14:2)
      1966 includes photocopy letter from Gerald R. Ford.
    - News Clippings, 1963 and 1969. (Box-folder 14:12)
    - News Clippings, 1971 and 1970. (Box-folder 14:15)
    - News Clippings, 1972 - 1974, and 1977. (Box-folder 14:17)
  - Other papers, 1967-1979. (Box 14)
    - The Reconstruction Amendments Debates, 1967. (Box-folder 14:5)
      The Convention and Constitutions of Virginia, 1776-1966.
    - Report of 1927 Virginia Constitution Committee on Amendments, 1968. (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Committee on Constitution Revision, 1968. (Box-folder 14:8)
    - Committee on Constitution Revision, 1969. (Box-folder 14:9)
    - Revision of State Constitution (Literature), 1968 - 1969. (Box-folder 14:10)
    - Poll Tax in Virginia, 1969. (Box-folder 14:11)
    - Ted Dalton's Tenth Anniversary as Federal Judge, 1969. (Box-folder 14:14)
    - Sigma Nu Fraternity and personal photographs, 1978., Photographs. (Box-folder 14:22)
    - Christmas Hunting Stories, 1967 - 1979. (Box-folder 14:23)
  Series 11: Photographs, Videotapes, etc.
- Photographs, Videotapes, and other artifacts. 1932-1956. (Box 15-16 and small box)
  - Ted Dalton for Governor bumper sticker, n.d. (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Three reels of tape, 1955-1956., 3 items. Tape. (Box-folder 15:2)
    Blacksburg Referendum speech, 1955; Capital Press Room, 1956; second reel of Blacksburg Referendum speech.
  - Reel of film entitled "Ted and Family", n.d., 1 item. Film. (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Three reels of Tape concerning the gubernatorial campaign, n.d., 3 items. Tape. (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Six photographs, 1942-1949, n.d., 6 items. Photographs. (Box-folder 15:5)
    Photographs include Virginia delegation to national Republican convention, Chicago 1932 (Ted Dalton); Indian Valley Hunt Club, Nov. 1942; (Ted Dalton): Rep. Lincoln Day Dinner, Feb. 1949; selection comm. At Eisenhower Vacation HQ, Augusta, GA., April 10; (Pres. Eisenhower, Ted Dalton): Judge Roby C. Thompson; Judges Ted Dalton, Alfred P. Murrah, and Oren Lewis.
  - Reel of film, n.d., 1 item. Film. Damaged. (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Nine Record albums, 1947-1953, n.d., 9 items. Albums. (Box-folder 16:2)
    The albums include Calir De Lune B/W Leibesstraum; Acceptance Speech, 1953 (2 Cv); Political Speech, 1951; Speech, 1947.
  - Three reels of film, n.d., 3 items. Film. (Othertype Small Box)
    The reels are entitled "Ted and Friends"; "Ted and Family"; and "Carry Virginia Back to Her People".
  - Five reels of tape, n.d., Tape. 5 items. (Othertype Small Box)
    Tapes contain campaign speeches.